Special Kalbi.
Burnt.
Eh, it's burning?
Hizu's spicy 35 hace extension
I'm Miyu Murayama, Sakurazaka 463rd year student, and this is my first Sakurazaka channel.
Today I'm going to Asakusa by myself.
Sky Tree.
I came to Asakusa thinking I'd like to go to yakiniku alone, but...
There's so many people
I've never been outside this area during the day, so I'd like to go on an adventure.
I've been to a yakiniku restaurant near here a few times with third term students
I've been to Yakiniku several times with my 3rd term students but the place we're going to today is not the one we usually go to with our 3rd term students.
I usually go to yakiniku restaurants with third term students.
I went to a yakiniku restaurant for lunch.
I'm sure it's going to be a little bit better than the other yakiniku restaurants we usually go to.
Fell down fell down fell down
Let's see...
I'm going to go to a better yakiniku restaurant than I usually go
I'm going to a better yakiniku restaurant
I see it!
Soon Hong Ri Restaurant.
It's a little bit austere and looks delicious.
I wanted to try authentic yakiniku by myself.
So I decided to go here.
Enter the commuter's book.
Welcome
Welcome, please come in
Yes, welcome
Bon appétit
Bon appétit.
Bon appétit!
Wow.
People people people people people people people
People
Light, main.
Excuse me.
Thank you very much for coming to our store today.
Yes, ma'am.
May I start with a drink?
Drinks.
This way, please.
Uh...
Green tea, please.
Yes, green tea is the tea.
I'll wait for your drink first.
Yes, sir.
I'm nervous inside, too.
They have samgyeopsal, too.
Samgyeopsal.
Halami and samgyeopsal.
Is it possible to make a half portion?
We can prepare all the meats in half portions.
Halami
Harami
Wave Halami, is that right?
Half a portion of "Wave Harami"?
I beg your pardon.
Harami.
Yes.
Tongue.
What's the difference between this and tongue?
The top tongue is sliced a little thicker than the one in the picture here.
Wave tongue is a thin slice.
It's thinner.
It's half of thin tongue.
Half.
Thank you very much.
Would you like some rice with that?
Rice is fine.
Show rice is fine.
Shaw rice, with an extra side of Ashley.
Yes, ma'am.
All right.
I've been really into barbecue lately, so I've been having some with some of the guys.
Bon appétit.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
I'll be right with you.
Okay. - Okay.
Something came, but I couldn't make it out.
I don't know what it is.
Leaves
In
what
What is it?
Oh.
Properly.
Yeah. - Yeah.
It's a good show.
I don't know what this is.
Let's grill it.
Is it tongue?
Is this tongue?
Excuse me.
Thank you very much.
This is tongue.
Bon appétit.
Wait.
No problem.
Bon appétit.
It's great!
My lunch set
My lunch set.
It's burning, it's burning, it's burning, it's burning, it's burning.
It's burning, burning, burning, burning.
Oh, my God.
It's burning.
I wonder if it's ready.
It looks too good to be true.
I don't know how to tell...
Or if this is it.
Hmm.
I'd better ask him.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Is this burnt?
I think it's done.
Thank you very much.
It looks burnt.
I'm going to cry.
My first tan.
It's my first tan
I'm crying
Five servings and a half portion of kaminamizu!
This is a customer of our customer
Hello!
Here's an addition.
It's Shonamizu for five!
This is a customer of our customer
Delicious!
This is a customer of ours
This is a customer of our customer
Delicious!
I'm going to grill the calami
I'm going to bake some kalami.
Here we go.
I'm going to try it.
Delicious!
Calami is my favorite!
Calami is my favorite
It feels good to grill the calami
Kara daughter
Kara tiers
Kara 모
Kara neither
Crentin
Push
Crentin Push
Hey. Hey.
Is this burnt?
It's a little burnt.
Hesser, that looks good.
Is it done?
Wow, it looks so good!
What shall we do?
Yay!
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Yum! Yum!
Dark nose
Cold 농
Kanka
deer
cold deer
Delicious!
You should eat it.
I'll have some.
Looks delicious.
I haven't had much loin either.
I don't know what a loin is.
Flip it over, if you don't mind.
Oh!
Looks good.
I wonder if it's in there.
I've never had it all before.
I mean, really, I've been here a million times.
I mean, I've never been in charge of a panel.
I've never even ordered anything.
Shizuki...
Nagi and the others would do it for me.
I've never done that before.
It's my first time.
Roast
I'll try it.
Delicious!
It's today.
I'll eat it.
Questment
Stirring
Coating.
I've never seen that before.
MERRY.
Three.
Phew.
Anyway
Oyster Gaza
vibrer inside
cafe
delicious
delicious!
I'll order something.
Here you go.
Top kalbi.
I don't even know what kalbi is.
I'm curious.
I'm a little curious.
That looks really good.
I think I'll have the special kalbi.
I want to order it.
I wonder if I can.
People keep asking me.
I don't know what kalbi is.
I'd like to order some.
It's soda.
Top of the line ribs.
Looks delicious.
I'll take a picture of it.
I'll take a picture of the ribs.
Excuse me.
Sorry, sir.
I can't do it. I can't order.
It's ready, it's ready, it's ready.
Looks good.
Excuse me.
I'll have half of the prime rib.
Sauce?
Yes, please.
That's all, please.
Yes, that's all.
Here you go.
Here's the Harami I grew up with.
Put lemon on it.
Delicious!
How is it? Looks delicious!
This is absolutely delicious!
Yum! Yum!
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Bon appétit!
Yes, I'll have some!
Half of the special ribs.
Delicious!
Delicious.
I'm going!
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going
Speed up. Packed dinner.
Yes, it's a shaped meal.
Cheese cheese cheese cheese
Queo butter.
Cheese and grandmother's milk.
Delicious!
Superb ribs!
Togo shi
Yum!
Delicious!
Sparkling!
I can't wait to try it!
I'll definitely try it again.
Eat!
Eat.
Food, get it?
I'll take it.
Go.
Why not?
I don't usually eat rice.
I don't know...
It's not that I'm skipping it or anything.
I don't have a chance to eat rice at all.
That's why
It's such an extravagant
food
It's a huge fire!
Mushrooms are on fire.
The fire is loving it.
Char, char, char, char.
This one's burnt.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Bon appétit!
This retarche.
It's cold.
Shut up.
This one's burnt.
Oooh.
I got burned over here.
Uh-oh.
This one's burnt.
Yes, this one.
This is delicious.
Looks delicious.
We shot a music video for our third season song the day before yesterday.
It was fun.
We got a lot of really good pictures.
Cute guys!
Aren't they cute?
I don't feel it.
Carina
Ripping
Hey, I got a knack for that.
Mercy.
It's like cheese.
It's fun!
It's fun.
I'm okay.
Loose video
I want to bring you all
It's so delicious!
Absolutely.
I bet you look good, Cleave and all.
Thanks for the food
Thank you very much.
I thought this chicken had a nice texture...
Mr. doctor is crispy too
olen
Gochujang
Ho faux
Yes, it was a little cold inside.
Oh well.
Delicious!
Was it good?
Thank you for the food.
It was delicious.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for the food.
It's my first time to eat Yakiniku by myself.
I like Asakusa, too.
I'd like to do some kind of food walking
I'd like to try it next time!
Invite someone!
I think I'm going to be addicted to yakiniku.
I'll post it again when I go to yakiniku by myself.
Something.
Heh.
That's very kind of you. The world alone.
Hey, guys.
It was good.
Oh, let me know if you go, here.
Bye-bye.
Mmm.